export const data = {
  title: "Color Blocks",
  description: `
    Kamu harus mencari 1 block warna yang berbeda dengan blok warna lainnya dengan waktu yang ditentukan!
  `,
};

export const levels = {
  1: {
    rows: 3,
    3: {
      1: {
        question: "#a82216",
        answer: "#5c0000",
      },
      2: {
        question: "#e35b00",
        answer: "#873600",
      },
      3: {
        question: "#c4b100",
        answer: "#948600",
      },
      4: {
        question: "#6aff00",
        answer: "#56cf00",
      },
      5: {
        question: "#00ba44",
        answer: "#00c94a",
      },
      6: {
        question: "#12b87b",
        answer: "#12b076",
      },
      7: {
        question: "#268784",
        answer: "#24807d",
      },
      8: {
        question: "#2f547a",
        answer: "#325880",
      },
      9: {
        question: "#3232ad",
        answer: "#3131a8",
      },
      10: {
        question: "#7c1d99",
        answer: "#801e9e",
      },
    },
  },
};
